Nancy L. Johnson Papers 2007.0008
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Inventory, undated, 1983-2006
  - Form letters, 1985 (Box 78)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 79)
    - He - Hix
    - H - Hl
    - Nancy Johnson, Sponsored Bills
    - State of Connecticut, New Manufacturing Firms
    - Aa - Am
    - An - Az
    - Ba - Bas
    - Bat - Bi
    - Bj - Bow
  - Science, Environment, Arts and Education, undated, 1990-2006 (Box 80)
    - 109th Congressional Stem Cell Research Briefing Book
    - Connecticut River Legislation, 2002
    - Climate Change
    - NEA--Arts, FY 2006
    - NEA, 2005
    - Arts-- NEA/ NEH, FY 2001-2003
    - Arts-- Connecticut groups
    - Long Island Sound
    - Candlewood Lake
    - Broadwater project
    - Brookfield Compressor station
    - Land Trusts
    - Clean Air
    - HR 303 Clean Air--Conference Report, Parts I and II, 1990, October 26
    - Clean Water
    - Clean Water (Metal Finishers)
    - Natural Resources Issues, 2003-2006
    - LIHEAP/Fuel Assistance
    - Superfund, 1994
    - Housatonic Valley National Heritage Area--Study and Designations, 1999-2006
    - WILDPAC
    - Anti-Drilling (Dear Colleague)
    - ANWR ( Artic National Wildlife Refuge), 2001-2002
    - Nancy Johnson/Talking points ANWR
  - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 81)
    - Di - Dn
    - Ea - Eh
    - Ei - En
    - Eo - Ez
    - Fa - Fh
    - Dr. Fanning
    - Fi - Fn
    - Fo - Fz
    - Ga - Gh
    - Gi - Gn
    - Go - Gr
    - Gs - Gz
    - Ha - Haq
    - Har - Haz
    - Na - Nh
    - Ni - Nn
    - No - Nz
    - Oa - Om
    - On - Oz
  - Letters re: Legislation and other topics, 1983-1988 (Box 82)
    - General Aviation Airspace
    - Eastern Airlines Pension
    - Armenian HJRes 132
    - El Salvador--Refugee Asylum
    - Ban loans to Communists
    - Emergency Planning Committee mailing
    - Free Angola
    - Iran Arms deal
    - Central America Report, "no letter"
    - Human Rights in India
    - Gorbachev visit
    - North Africa n Jews
    - Gaza Riots
    - National Endowment Event invite
    - Iran ian Airbus Victims
    - Math/Science Fair (poster)
    - Animal Welfare
    - Refugees (update)
    - Foreign Exchange program
    - Arms Control Follow up
    - Central America (con)
    - Federal Retirement COLA
    - Town Hall meetings
    - Project Excellence in Education, Letter #1
    - Education Advisory Group meeting
    - Trade Bill (Gephardt, Pro)
    - Trade Letter to Electronics Companies
    - Uncompensated Overtime
    - Military Retirement
    - Forget-me-Not flag
  - Issue Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 83)
    - Iroquois Pipeline, E-09011, Packet 2, 1987 June 18
    - Central America (pro) updated and follow up, 6-11008, 1986 April 25
    - Nicaragua-Covert aid (con), update and follow up, D-11026, 1986 March 14
    - Central America (con), update, H-11026, 1987 August 31
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 84)
    - Ha - Haq
    - Har - Haz
    - He - Hn
    - Ho - Hs
    - Ia - Iz
    - Ja - Jm
    - Jn - Jz
    - Ka
    - Ke - Kh
    - Ki - Kq
    - Kr - Kz
    - La - Ld
    - Le - Lg
    - Lh - Ln
    - Lo - Lz
    - Mac - Maz
    - McA - McI
    - McK - McV
    - Me - Mh
    - Mi - Mm
    - Mn - Mz
    - Na - Nh
    - Ni - Nn
    - No - Nz
    - Oa - Om
    - On - Oz
  - Votes and Bills, 1983-1987 (Box 85)
  - Select Committee on Children, Youth and Families, House of Representatives, Hearing and Reports, 1985-1988 (Box 86)
    - 99th Congress, v. 1-3
    - 100th Congress, v. 1-3
  - Appropriations/Earmarks, undated (Box 87)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 88)
    - Ht - Hz
    - Ia - Iz
    - Ja - Jm
    - Jn - Jz
    - Ka - Kd
    - Ke - Kh
    - Ki - Kq
    - Kr - Kz
    - La - Ld
    - Le - Li
    - Lj - Ln
    - Lo - Lz
    - Luca Case
    - Ma - Mb
    - McA - McJ
    - McK - McZ
    - Me - Mh
    - Mi - Mm
    - Mn - Mz
    - Pa - Pd
    - We
  - Subject Files, 1983-1986 (Box 89)
    - Arms control
    - Friends
    - Environmentalists
    - Labor
    - Local Government Officials
    - Mass Mailings: Seniors
    - Sportsmen
    - Veterans
    - Women
    - Mass Mailings
    - Small Business
    - Human Services
    - Education reports
    - Town Hall meeting file
    - Procurement Conference
    - Jobs Conference
    - Small Business Conference
    - Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA)
    - Women in Business
    - Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA) notes
    - Office charts
    - Fall Planning
    - Educational Town Hall meeting reports
    - Swearing in Trip to D.C.
    - Star Wars lecture
    - Polanco Case
    - Youth Employment Conference
    - Public Service Career/Academy Day
    - PAC Monring meetings
    - Friends Trip
    - Agricultural Forum
    - NLJ Chamber Trip to Saratoga, NY
    - Super Letters File, 1985-1986
    - Open Convention Information
    - Business-Higher Education Conference
    - CT JPTA Conference
  - Votes and Bills, 1985 (Box 90)
  - Unorganized Correspondence, 1985 (Box 91)
  - Form Letter responses, 1986 (Box 92)
  - Special Projects, 1983-1985 (Box 93)
    - Fall Special Projects
    - Franking Commission Reports
    - Agricultural Forum
    - District hearings
    - Fafner Bearing
    - Homebased Business Conference
    - Small Business Conference
    - Pre-Retirement Conference
    - Procurement Conference
    - Career Changes Conference
    - Economic Development Project
    - Senior Citizen Intern program
    - Hispanic Advisory Group
    - Washington Conference on Foreign Policy
    - Super Letters 98th Congress
    - Super File
    - Enterprise Zones
    - NLRB File--Dotson Letter
    - Specialty Steel
    - Gas Turbines
    - JTPA
    - Davis-Bacon Information
  - Bills, 1983 (Box 94)
  - Town Files, Avon - Danbury, 1986-2007 (Box 95)
    - Avon
    - Barkhamstead
    - Bethel
    - Bethlehem
    - Bridgewater
    - Bristol
    - Bristol grants
    - Bristol--Town companies
    - Brookfield
    - Burlington
    - Canaan/North Canaan
    - Canton
    - Cheshire
    - Colebrook
    - Cornwall
    - Danbury
  - MMA, 2003 (Box 96)
  - Form letters, undated (Box 97)
  - Clippings, 1984 (Box 98)
  - Clippings, 1984 (Box 99)
  - Health Care Files, 1993-2007 (Box 100)
    - Ambulance Fee Schedule
    - Companies: Cost Containing Plans
    - Amubulances-- Connecticut
    - 340B pricing
    - Appropriations--Earmarks, 2005
    - Budget--FY07 President's
    - Appropriations--LHHS Amendments
    - Appropriations--Earmarks, 2006
    - LHHS--FY07
    - Areas on Aging
    - Budget--President '06 Hearings
    - ASCs
    - Budget--President'06
    - ConnPACE
    - Covering Kids
    - Connecticut Children's Hospital
    - Dentists
    - DME Competitive Bidding
    - DRA--Cost-Sharing
    - DRA--Medicaid Drug REimbursement
    - DRA--Asset Transfer
    - Diabetes
    - DME--Power Wheelchairs
    - DME--Suppliers
    - DME--Oxygen (DRA)
    - ED Amend
    - Excessive Charges
    - FDA--Pediatric Drugs
    - FDA--Clinical Trials
    - FDA--Expedited Access
    - FSA Rollover
    - HIPPA privacy Rule Modifications, 2001-2003
    - ICD-10
    - Health IT
      - Articles
      - H.R. 4157--ICD-10
      - Loans
      - Providers
      - AHIMA
      - H.R. 4157 Comments
      - Bills in 109th
      - Connecticut
      - H.R. 4157 Confidentiality/Security
      - H.R. 4157/CBO estimate
      - H.R. 4157/CBO
      - H.R. 4157 Full Committee markup
      - H.R. 4157 Florr bill with transparency
    - Executive order--Tech./Quality/Tranparency
    - H.R. 4157--Endorsement letter
    - Health IT--H.R. 4157--Interoperability
    - RedLine
    - Health IT
      - H.R. 4157 E&C/ W&M side-by-side
      - H.R. 4157 Standards Amendment
      - H.R. 4157 Standard modification process
      - H.R. 4157 Stark
      - Stark ACLA
      - VISTA (DVD)
      - S. 1418 Wired Act
      - H.R. 4157 Telehealth
      - H.R. 5971 Sue Kelly Bill
    - HSA--High Deductible
    - HSA--H.R. 6134 Hope Act HSA, 2006
    - Homecare-- Connecticut
    - Homercare--Health IT
    - Hopsice
    - Home Infusion Therapy
    - NIH Reform, 2006
    - Universal Health Care
    - Health Coverage Tax Credit
  - Personnel, undated (Box 101)
  - Town Files: Litchfield - Southington, undated (Box 102)
    - Litchfield
    - Meriden
    - Middlebury
    - Morris
    - New Fairfield
    - New Hartford
    - New Milford
    - Newtown
    - Norfolk
    - Plainville
    - Plymouth
    - Roxbury
    - Salisbury
    - Sherman
    - Simsbury
    - Simsbury: Ensign Bickford
    - Somers
    - Southbury
    - Southington
  - Town Files: East Granby - Kent, undated (Box 103)
    - East Granby
    - Enfield (includes Bigelow-Hartford Mill Complex)
    - Falls Village
    - Farmington
    - Farmington: Tunxis Community College
    - Goshen
    - Sharon
    - Sharon Hospital
    - Granby
    - Hartland
    - Harwinton
    - Kent (includes Schaghticoke/ BIA)
  - Clippings, 2002-2006 (Box 104)
  - Budget, OSHA, Teen pregnancy, Veterans, Affirmative Action, undated (Box 105)
  - Pension, trade- China, undated (Box 106)
  - Clinical research, Ambulance, Stark II, SNF, undated (Box 107)
  - New Britain files, undated (Box 108)
    - City government
    - Grants
    - Events attended
    - History/Accomplishments
    - Cases
    - Conferences
    - Businesses
    - Police
    - Arch Street, NRZ
    - Broad Street, NRZ
    - North Oak, NRZ
    - Veterans
    - Clubs
    - Churches
    - Museum of American Art
    - NAACP
    - Trinity on Main
    - Literacy Volunteers of Central Connecticut
    - Schools
    - Social Services
    - Stanley Works
    - Prudence Crandall Center
    - Friendship Center
    - YMCA/YWCA/Boys & Girls Club
    - Resources
    - Klingberg
    - Pathways Senderos
    - Headstart/HRA
    - Central Connecticut State University
  - Health, Ambulance, Children, Conn-PACE, Health IT, HSAs, undated (Box 109)
  - Form letters, undated (Box 110)
  - Regulatory reform, Medicare, Pension, Welfare, Human Resources, undated (Box 111)
  - New Britain, undated (Box 112)
  - Connecticut Subject/Interest Group Files, undated (Box 113)
    - Mashantucket Pequot Tribe
    - Indian file
    - Medicare
    - Audubon
    - National Wildlife Federation
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association
    - Quinnipiac River
    - Connecticut River Watershed Council
    - Shepaug River
    - Schaghticoke Tribal Nation
    - New Britain General Hospital
    - Muslim-American
    - Pakistan i
    - Metacomet-Mattabesset Trails meeting
    - Mettabesset River Watershed
    - LAke Waramaug
    - USGS
    - American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee
    - Farmington River Watershed Association (FRWA)
    - Sierra Club
    - Pomperaug River Watershed
    - nature Conservancy
    - Environmental learning Centers of Connecticut
    - The arts: NEA/ NEH
    - Black-American
    - New Britain Hispanic Community, including Puerto Rican file
    - Polish American Congress/Polish Organization and history
    - Polish Community
    - Lithuanian
    - Jewish
    - Ethics: Gingrich case
  - Medical Issues, 1995-2007 (Box 114)
    - Interoperability--108th Congress
    - Cancer Care
    - Drug Overuse Hearing planning, 2005
    - Specialty hospitals
    - Small Issues--107th Congress
    - Small Issues--108th Congress
    - Home Care--Medicare
    - Medicare and Choice, 2000-circa 2004
    - Medicare Select bill, 1995
    - Medicare Bill, 1995
    - Medicare, 1995
    - Health Savings Accounts
    - Patient Safety--"Errors" bill, HR 4889, 2002
  - Press Clippings and news outlets, 1985-1987 (Box 115)
    - Newsletter, 1985-1986
    - 1985 January - February
    - 1985 March 1 - June
    - 1985 July - December
    - 1986 January - February
    - 1986 March - April
    - 1986 May - June
    - 1986 July - August
    - 1986 September
    - 1986 October
    - 1986 November
    - 1986 December
    - Jeff Denny Radio show, 1986 - 1987 July
  - Education and Environment Files, undated, 1980-2006 (Box 116)
    - Education
    - Issues: NCLB/Education
    - Education, Title IX
    - Education, 109th Congress
    - Unidentified file
    - E-Rate
    - NEA-CEA
    - Trio-Gear Up
    - Education Appropriations
    - Vouchers
    - College Affordability
    - Education, 1997
    - Environment
    - Farmington River Wild and Scenic, Designation and Studies, 1980-1985
    - Farmington River Wild and Scenic, Designation and Studies, 1985-2006
    - Legislation cosponsored by NLJ in 104th Congress as of 8/8/1996
  - Clippings, 1989-1995 (Box 117)
  - Disease Management, Price transparency, Social Security, Hospital, undated (Box 118)
  - Chairman Hearing Binders #2, Committee on Ways and Means, Subcommittee on Health, 2001-2006 (Box 119)
    - Medicare's geographic cost adjustments, 2002 July 23
    - Nation's uninsured, 2001 April 4
    - MedPAC's March report on Medicare payment policies, 2006 March 1
    - National coverage determination, 2005 May 5
    - Emergency care, 2006 July 27
    - Medicare chronic care improvement program, 2004 May 11
    - Value-based purchasing for physicians under Medicare
    - Medicare payments to physicians, 2005 February 10
    - Physician paymnets, 2002 February 28
  - Susan Christensen Health Files, undated (Box 120)
  - Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 121)
  - Chairman Hearing Binders #2, Committee on Ways and Means, Subcommittee on Health, 1998-2005 (Box 122)
    - Tax law health insurance, W&M oversight, 1998 April 23
    - Gainsharing, 2005 October 7
    - Competition in the FEHB program, and its effect on prices for health care services, 2005 December 2
    - Physician-owned specialty hospitals, 2005 March 8
    - Medicare reimbursement of physician-administered drugs, 2006 July 13
    - Health Care information technology (4th in series), 2006 April 6
    - Health care information technology, 2005 July 27
    - Health care information technology, 2004 June 17
    - Implementation of the Medicare drug benefit, 2006 May 3
  - Photographs, undated (Box 123)
  - Part D, Physician SGR, Physician payment, Stem Cell, Transparency, Wage Index, undated (Box 124)
  - Ways and Means, Medical prescriptions, Medicare, Stem Cells, Medicaid, Connecticut Hospitals, undated (Box 125)
  - Hospital financing, MMA, Mental Health, Oncology, undated (Box 126)
  - Marc Buckley's Banking, Foreign Affairs, Defense files, undated (Box 127)
  - Susan Christensen Health Files, undated (Box 128)
  - Photographs, 1984-1988 (Box 129)
  - Campaign files, 1986-1996 (Box 130)
    - Congress Campaign (2 folders), 1986
    - Congress Campaign--Finaance (3 folders), 1988
    - Congress Campaign--Field (3 folders), 1988
    - Congress Campaign--Field, Scheduling, Neighbors of NJ, Volunteers, Towns (4 folders), 1986
    - Congress Campaign--Issues, media (4 folders), 1996
  - Campaign Files, 1984-1986 (Box 131)
  - Appropriations, Crime, Justive, undated (Box 132)
  - Campaign Files, undated, 1984-2002 (Box 133)
    - Congress Campaign--Speeches, Issues, 1984
    - Articles about NJ, undated
    - Congress Campaign--Primary, General (2 folders), 1982
    - Democrats for NJ, 1982
    - Opposition Research (on NJ), 1979-1980
    - Congress Campaign--Towns (3 folders), 1994
    - Congress Campaign--Finance (3 folders), 2002
    - Congress Campaign--Finance (3 folders), 1986
    - Congress Campaign (3 folders), 1984
    - Congress Campaign--Issues (5 folders), 1984
  - Issue, Campaign files, 1994-2006 (Box 134)
    - Congress Campaign--Field (4 folders), 1996
    - Congress Campaign--Book 1 (4 folders), 1994
    - Active form letters (4 folders), 2006
    - Congress Campaign--Finance (4 folders), 1996
    - Congress Campaign--Book 2 (3 folders), 1994
    - Congress Campaign--Press (3 folders), 1984
  - Campaign files, 1990-2004 (Box 137)
    - Congress Campaign (4 folders), 1992
    - Congress Campaign--Finance (3 folders), 1990
    - Congress Campaign--Field (3 folders), 2000
    - Congress Campaign--Press (4 folders), 2000
    - Congress Campaign--Finance (3 folders), 2000
    - Bush, George W. Event, 2003 June 13
    - Congress Campaign--Finance (3 folders), 2002
    - Congress Campaign (4 folders), 2004
  - Medicare Debate and Campaign Files, undated, 2002-2004 (Box 138)
    - Medicare Debate (2 folders), 2002
    - Campaign notebook (2 folders), 2002
    - Re-elect NLJ to Congress Committee, Press and Media (3 folders), 2002 November
    - Johnson for Congress, Field organization (2 folders), 2004
    - Accomplihments/record
  - Press, Media, Finance, 1997-1998 (Box 139)
  - Campaign Files, 1984-2002 (Box 140)
    - Congress Campaign--Press (4 folders), 1984
    - Cheney, Dick Event, 2002 July 15
    - Congress Campaign--Documentation 23:1 (2 folders), 2002
    - Congress Campaign--Field (3 folders), 2002
    - Congress Campaign (4 folders), 2002
    - Bush, George W. Event (2 folders), 2002 April 9
    - Schaus, Nick, 1982
    - Congress Campaign--Finance, 1992
    - Congress Campaign (3 folders), 1990
  - Campaign Files, 1986-1998 (Box 141)
    - Congress Campaign--Press, 1998
    - Congress Campaign, 1986
    - Congress Campaign--Field (4 folders), 1998
  - Town Files, Avon - Hartford, undated (Box 142)
  - Scenic and historic book, undated (Box 143)
  - Temporary Office Files, undated, 1987-2006 (Box 144)
    - Realia
    - Reagan visit originals list, 1987 July 8
    - Social Security
    - Memorable Moments
    - UConn Speech: Talking points, testimony in Committee and Rules, Statements on bills
    - Speeches: Health, Lincoln Day, Commencement, etc.
    - Health Care--Speech info.
    - Hearing on Post-Acute care, 2005 June 16
    - Hearing on Long term care, 2005 June 19
    - Town Hall meetings, 2003 April
    - Tributes, UConn (contains DVD)
    - Articles
    - IRS: Taxpayer Advocate visit, 1999
    - Hearing on e-prescribing, 2004 July 22
  - Health Care Files, undated (Box 145)
    - Health: VNA
    - Part D--Home Infusion Therapy
    - Home care--Nurses
    - Hospital
    - Connecticut Hospital Association
    - Bristol Hospital
    - St. Francis Hospital file
    - Hartford Hospital
    - Hospital for Special Care, New Britain
    - New Britain General Hospital
    - NBGH/CHC/Nursing homes/HHC
    - New Milford Hospital
    - University of Connecticut
    - Connecticut State Medical Society
    - Physicians issues (2 folders)
  - Correspondence, Issue and Subject Files, undated (Box 146)
    - Realia
    - Nice letters, 2006
    - Nice letters, 2005
    - Nice letters, 2004
    - Nice letters, 2003
    - Nice letters, 2002
    - Letters, 1990s
    - Thank yous, 1983-1984
    - Campaign Finance reform
    - Arts, NEA- NEH
    - Sportsman/ NRA
    - University of Hartford
    - Yale University
    - Kaman Corporation
    - United Technologies
    - UPS
    - Tax seminar, Ways and Means-Joint Tax, 2002
  - Social and Health Care Issues, undated, 1999-2005 (Box 147)
    - Welfare-Work Issues, 1999
    - Bookings, Comments: Teen Pregnancy and prevention
    - Women's Issues
    - Abortion
    - Alzheimer's Association
    - District H.C. Providers, Managed care plans/Others
    - Uninsured, 2004-2005
    - Mental Health
  - Medicare reform, Clinton-Michael, undated, 1995-2000 (Box 148)
  - Videos, undated (Box 149)
  - Videos, undated (Box 150)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 151)
  - Videos, electronic data, CDs, undated (Box 152)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 153)
  - Campaign materials (Tshirts), undated